To me Korea means a second home
With so many faces letting me know I ain't alone
In the land of smart phones
Some are sweatin' off the spice
But if you into something different you can try the fried rice
Subways full of peace and quiet
T-Money in my back pocket
In case I'm taking a ride
From my soul to Seoul
With the help of Scotty Soul
Korea is full of life I know you're feeling
it Saul
So much culture
My favorite 닭갈비 (stir-fried spicy chicken)
Life's so fast that we call it "빨리 빨리"
To the beach of Busan I'm trying to make it in a hurry
Trying to have a good time
I'm chillin' with my honey
So much to explore
You know you want more
They ask you how you're doing tell 'em, "좋아요!"
"맞다 맞다!" (That's right, that's right!")
Korea is the place where you wanta
Turn up from the summertime all the way to winter
From Haeundae beach to Itaewon
I don't need to have a worry 'cuz I got that
won
From Haeundae beach to Itaewon
I don't need to have a worry 'cuz I got that won
From Seoul to Busan
I'm trying to see it all the way to Gunsan
Cuz' this place is only showing me a good time
So join me on the journey to the good life
the good life
Let me hear you say
I moved out to Yongin then I went to Bundang
If you don't live in Seoul son tell me what are you on
Ask me when I'll go home and I'll tell you, "언젠가" (someday)
I ain't living nowhere that ain't got 감자탕
노래방 (karaoke bar) four in the morn' my favorite song
We all gotta work tomorrow 잔 하나만
Everybody speak that language of that la la la
But I'm starting to learn the 가사 (lyrics) to the 아리라리랑
곱창 막창 다 좋아 (곱창 막창, it's all good)
곱창 막창 뭐가 달라 (곱창 막창, what's the difference?)
곱창 막창 나 몰라 (곱창 막창, I don't know)
곱창 막창 먹자 먹자 먹자
See all my homies swoopin' on the Hangang
Sippin' bubbly in Hongdae, Hongdae
It's 1,000 won to get to Gangnam
But you gotta be a little quiet on the subway
I'm talking about the R.O.K. and what it is to me
I'm talking about the R.O.K. and what it is
Let me hear you say, "한국위하여!"
한국위하여